（春野はるのサクラ）ん！
（サクラ）
これじゃ うかつに近づけない
I can't carelessly approach him
like this.
What intense heat and flames.
（チヨ）なんという高熱の炎じゃ
（サクラ）あと １分半
（チヨ）うむ
One and a half minutes left.
Yes.
（サソリ）死ね ババア
Die, Grandma!
（チヨ）ん？
（サクラ）あっ
（チヨ）これでも食らえ
Eat this!
（サソリ）甘いな
You wish!
やはりな　あの戦闘の最中に
チャクラ糸を仕込んでやがったか
Just as I thought.
You attached a Chakra thread
in the middle of that fight, huh?
But the same trick won't work twice!
だが 同じ手が通用するかよ
残念だったな
How unfortunate.
（サクラ）くっ 時間が…
There's no time...
♪～
～♪
Puppet Fight: 10 vs. 100!
What's the matter...?
Aren't you going to attack?
どうした？ こないのか
The effects of the antidote
will last one more minute...
（サクラ）解毒効果は あと１分
Then...
（サソリ）ならば…
Water?
水… サクラ！ 離れろ！
Sakura! Get away!
あっ…
あっ！
うっ…
（サソリ）そらっ！
There!
いつまで 逃げ回ってるつもりだ
How long do you intend
to run about?
ハア ハア ハア…
（サクラ）あと… 20秒
Twenty seconds left.
そういうことなら…
If that's how it's going to be...
ハッ
おっ…
ううっ
（サクラ）あと15秒
Fifteen seconds...left...
（チヨ）大丈夫か！ サクラ！
Are you okay, Sakura?!
（サソリ）死ね！
Die!
チヨバア様！ ううっ…
Granny Chiyo!
あっ…
うっ…
（サクラ）解毒薬は効いてる
あとは 傷の痛みさえ耐えれば…
The antidote is working!
If I can just endure the pain...
フッ… ムダな努力だ
Your efforts are futile.
ああっ
（サクラ）あと５秒！
Five seconds left!
Four seconds.
４秒！
You little--!
このおお！
（チヨ）サクラか
Sakura?!
しゃーんなろー！
Cha!
（サクラ）３秒！
Three seconds.
Two!
２！
Scorpion
（サクラ）ハア ハア…
ハア… ううっ…
ハア ハア
（サクラ）ちょうど
解毒薬の持続時間内に 倒せた
We were able to beat him
exactly within the sustained duration
of the antidote...
ハア ハア フフッ…
We did it.
やりました
チヨバア様… やりましたよ！
Granny Chiyo, we did it!
サクラ お前…
Sakura...
You...
フフッ
（デイダラ）あのガキ…
すっかり おとなしくなったな…
That kid...has totally calmed down...
何をたくらんでる？ うん
What's he planning?
（うずまきナルト）
カカシ先生 まだかよ
Kakashi Sensei!
Aren't you ready yet?!
（はたけカカシ）そう焦るなって
Hold your horses...
俺は お前ほど
チャクラを持ってないからな
I don't have as much Chakra
as you, after all...
時間がかかるんだよ
It's going to take time.
（サクラ）んっ…
Scorpion
（サソリ）何をやったって…
What did you do?
ハッ…
That's right.
（チヨ）そうじゃなあ
やるのは これからじゃ
The fight is just beginning.
これは己で禁じた術
This is a Jutsu I myself sealed...
２度と使うまいと思っておったが…
I didn't think I'd ever use it again...
そうも いかんようじゃ
But it seems it won't work out
that way.
これで幕引きにしようぞ
Now let's put an end to this.
（サソリ）傀儡使いは…
It's said the ability of
a puppet master is measured
使える傀儡の数で
その者の能力が計れると言われるが
by the number of puppets they can use...
さすが ババアだ
I'd expect no less from you, Grandma.
す… すごい数　10体も？
Th-There's so many...
Ten of them.
チヨバア極意の指の数
Granny Chiyo's secret
"Number of Fingers."
うわさには 聞いたが
I'd heard rumors about it...
それが城１つを
１人で落としたというカラクリ
The device you used to bring down
a castle by yourself...
白しろ秘技ひぎ･十機近松じゅっきちかまつの集
The Secret White Move:
Chikamatsu's 10 Puppets.
The ten masterpieces by Monzaemon,
傀儡の術
初代操演者 モンザエモンの十傑作
the first Puppeteer of
the Puppet Master Jutsu...
It's a great collection of puppets.
大した傀儡集だ
だがな！
However...
ハッ
I...
（サソリ）俺は
これで１国を落とした
used this to bring down a nation!
あっ…
（チヨ）こヤツ ここまで…
He's become...this powerful...
我ながら あきれる
I'm appalled at myself.
How long am I going to have to fight
a little girl and an old bag...?
小娘と老いぼれ相手に
いつまでやってんだか
最後のカラクリまで
見せることになるとはな
I never thought I'd have to
bring out my final device...
あっ…
Secret Red Move: Performance
of a Hundred Puppets...
（サソリ）赤あか秘技ひぎ･百機ひゃっきの操演
とくと見せてやる
I'll show you...
（チヨ）サクラ…
（サクラ）あっ…
Sakura...
お前は すでに解毒薬が切れとる
手を出すな
The effects of
your antidote have worn off.
Stay out of this.
うん？
You should already know...
もう分かってますよね　私の性格
my personality!
（チヨ）そうだな
性格も綱手つなで譲りだったな
That's right...
You've inherited
Tsunade's personality as well.
じゃがな これで終劇にするぞよ
覚悟はよいか
But let's make this the final act.
Are you ready?
（サクラ）はい！
Yes!
（サソリ）フッ
Here he comes!
（チヨ）くるぞよ
フン！
三宝吸潰さんぽうきゅうかい！
Three Treasures Suction Crush!
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
（サクラ）さすがに この数
With this many of them...
確実に数を減らすには
なんとか１対１に
The surefire way to lessen
the number
is to fight them one-on-one somehow...
（傀儡人形の動く音）
（サクラ）あっ！
All right!
よし！
There are too many of them!
（チヨ）数が多すぎる
（サクラ）くっ ハア ハア…
おっ くっ…
大丈夫か サクラ
Are you okay, Sakura?!
（サクラ）大丈夫です
I'm okay!
（チヨ）気を抜くでないぞ
Stay sharp!
Right!
（サクラ）はい！
（チヨ）サソリの傀儡は
確実に減っておる
There definitely aren't
as many of Sasori's puppets now...
じゃが ヤツの傀儡１体に対する集中力は
逆に上がっておるようじゃ
But conversely,
it looks like he's concentrating
more on each puppet now.
その上 解毒薬はあと１つ…
And on top of that,
we only have one antidote left.
わしかサクラのどちらかでも
傷つけば いきなりきつくなる
Things will get tough in a hurry
if either Sakura or I get wounded.
フッ…
（チヨ）はっ！
うわっ
（サクラ）あっ チヨバア様！
Granny Chiyo!
（チヨ）しまった
Oh no...!
大丈夫ですか？ チヨバア様
Are you okay, Granny Chiyo?
You don't need to worry about me!
わしの心配は無用じゃ
それより お主はサソリを狙え
More importantly, aim for Sasori.
ほかの傀儡は わしが抑える
I'll keep the other puppets in check!
はい！
Right!
（サクラ）ふん　あっ
サクラ！ それを使え！
Sakura, use that!
はっ！
ハア… ハア…
ハア ハア…
ここだあ！
Here!
（サソリ）おおっ…
（サクラ）ハア ハア…
ハア ハア… やった！
We did it!
ハア ハア ハア…
You can't move.
動けまい　その封印は
チャクラを完全に押さえ込むものじゃ
That seal completely
suppresses all Chakra.
もう… チャクラ糸は使えぬ
You can't use
your Chakra threads anymore.
終わりじゃよ サソリよ　ううっ…
It's over, Sasori...
（サクラ）
チヨバア様！ 早く解毒薬を！
Granny Chiyo!
Use the antidote quickly!
♪～
～♪
She was quick-witted
from the very beginning...
初めから頭のきれる子だったよ
And she was super cute...
それに ムチャクチャかわいかった
She was way too beautiful!
She was my youth!
ええ あまりにも美しすぎました
僕の青春でした
Despite her character,
she had her good points...
あれで 結構いいとこあったのよね
そうだな
こんなに 早く逝っちまうなんて
リー 俺の胸で泣け
ガイ先生！
俺たちを見守ってくれ
俺 絶対サクラちゃんのこと
忘れねえってばよ
ええい やめんか！
縁起でもない
次回「叶わぬ夢」
（サクラ）くノ一絵草紙(えぞうし)
（カカシ）今回の任務は
くノ一の調査だったな
各自が担当した
くノ一を報告してくれ
（ナルト･サクラ）了解！
（サクラ）それじゃ 私から
担当は 熱血ガイ班の紅一点
あらゆる 忍具を使いこなす
テンテンさん
（カカシ）こゆ～い メンツの中の
清涼剤ってとこだな
俺の担当は
幻術のエキスパート 紅くれないだ
（サクラ）へえ… 紅先生も
木ノ葉ベストを着ることあるんですね
（ナルト）お～し
最後は俺の番だな
（サクラ）…って これ
あんたの おいろけの術じゃない
（ナルト）ダハハハ　なかなかの
ボンッ キュッ ボンッだろう
さらに パワーアップした
新鋭の忍術 いくぜ！
（カカシ）おおっ
いいかげんにしろ！
ボハハ～ン！
イタイ タイタ～イ
（カカシ）こりゃ 新記録かな
（サクラ）ふんっ！
（ナルト）あ…